Tomorrow's chime has sounded. We are the CJB 7 school.
Attendance number 14, this is Macoino.
Attendance number 16, this is Scrinoma.
Attendance number 17, this is Manailuna.
Hello.
Today is the time to enjoy talking over dinner.
Okay, let's eat.
Then let's eat.
Okay.
Rino-san, what is it?
Rino-san, it's potato salad from McDonald's.
Oh...
Only vegetables.
I prepared natto as a topping of Coco Ich's curry with gooey shabu-shabu.
From what?
Zero.
I also prepared Coco Ichi's cabbage sticky shabu curry with mushroom topping and okara.
That's as good as it gets.
Bon appétit!
That's a little scary.
What is it, okara?
Wasn't it hee-hee?
Now?
The first time I ate at Coco Ichiba, I couldn't tell from the curry curry.
It was so spicy.
Ayane's first time doing the dough screening for the mountain oil.
Yes, the dough screening.
It's already been a month since I started.
Yes, it does.
Delicious.
It's spicy.
But it's okay.
Are you okay?
I wanted to eat Coco Ichi.
Are you old enough?
Yes, I am.
I don't like salads that much, but I can eat Mac Sara's.
It's delicious.
What's the side dish like?What's the side dish look like?
Hmm?
My eyes are getting sleepy?
My eyes are getting sleepy.
But it's so delicious.
What's your favorite topping at Coco Ichi?
I can't say.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
Do you have any recommendations?
I'm going to have dinner with you.
I'm not sure about eating cake or curry.
I'm doing it around.
I mean eating cake.
I really love my curry.
That's the pork shove curry.
What did you two order?
I was listening to you.
Oh my God, Princess Suwa.
I ordered the Pork Shove Curry with Mushroom Topping.
I had pork shove curry with natto topping and zero curry.
They both said pork shove curry.
But I see something interesting.
Interesting.
I hope it's a shingeki.
I wonder how many minutes before.
The three of us did "The Eye of the World" together.
Because we did three together too.
It was quiet as usual.
It's usually popular when Cocona is there,
What kind of senior is Cocona?
She is an older sister.
She is like an older sister.
Yuna-chan is a senior who is very close to you.
Nonoka is a very big sister.
She is like a senior.
And Nonoka?
Nonoka is also a senior at the same age.
Nonoka is my senior,
When we are together, regardless of baby choo,
When we have dinner together, she is really my sister.Like when I'm eating dinner, I really have a sister.
It's very meat head-like, but the insides are really
It smells like juke.
Cute.
Nonoka, you know, she has a lot of big sisters, big sisters.
And a lot of kids have a lot of sisters.
So you have one now?
Yes, I have three.
Emma seems to have a lot of older sisters.
She seems to have a lot of sisters.
She seems to have older sisters.
Me too.
Yuna acts like a big sister.
She's her sister's sister.
My big sister's big sister.
Natto no Yarn pops.
I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry.
What's your favorite dish?
Oh.
Definitely the spaghetti with sticky motsu.
Monja?
I like monja too.
If I said monja, would you say that's your favorite food?
Did I say I wouldn't say three?
Because you just said four.
So I'll say monja, three sticky buns, and spaghetti.
OK.
Now sushi and
Cucumber and
bread, and
I'm hungry.
Last.
Rahm, the ward.
I like this so much, I've never eaten it.
But it's yummy.
It's my favorite dish to cook, too, though it's not an ingredient.
But I like lettuce.
Yumo ingredients.
But I like to boil it more than raw.
I understand.I understand.
I'm going to want to be lonely because I'm also going to be boiling.
I'm taking pictures, because the day after tomorrow the one that doesn't stick out will start.
That's the only time it's a kaku. It is a super convenience food outside.
When it's sunny, it's sunny.
Is it sunny when it looks like it's sunny?
It's all over the place.
If you look at the various weather forecasts, it was disjointed.
They might say, "It was raining.
They might say it was sunny.
Certainly.
Sunny.
I want it to be sunny.
What do you like?
I don't know.
What kind of girl might make it rain?
What kind of girl could make it rain?
What song are you looking forward to the most?
JAPON
And Time Slope.
I like it here.
Is that a stick?
I don't know.
Was it not sharp enough?
I didn't think so.
I liked it natural.
Natural.
I did the natural.
When they go around the sub stage
When they go around the sub stage, they do this movement in the chorus.
At the beginning of the lesson
I'm not sure how I did it.
I was really on my toes.
I'm on my toes.
Don't look at me while I'm looking at you.
You do it.
I'll call Yuno-chan while I'm doing it.
Thanks for watching!
But it's so impossible.
It's really a talking candy.It's really a talking candy.
In the picture, it doesn't look like it's going to be too much, because it's going to be on the top.
I was thinking of going up and down.
When I was in junior high school, even if it was raining on the way home, there were people who wanted to brush a little bit, a lot, you know.
That's why.
I used to go home with my mother even when it was raining.
I admired that kind of thing.
I'm glad.
So far, KOKONNA is the one.
She doesn't even use an umbrella when it's raining.
Even with an umbrella.
I wonder what it's all about?
I haven't forgotten the order I took in middle school.
I've been told.
After that, I had to go home
I had to go to work or something.
Here, I'm walking to go on from another station road, and I saw you.
I'm not walking fast, I'm just going to use it.
I'm going to use it without hesitation.
I've been feeling so good all the time, it's a pain in the ass to put an umbrella on her.
But the thing is that Kokona-chan is having fun.
It's a hassle to carry it
It's a hassle to carry it.
It's a hassle to open it and walk around with it.
If you have a reason, there's nothing you can do.
Well, we don't think about that later, me and KOKONA-chan.
I'm not giving you a reason just because it's a pain in the ass right now.
That's love, isn't it?
The way you put it all together is too much fun!
Well, this one has too many people.
Take that one and hold it behind your back.
Oh, you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
But I had to move from one side of the room to the other while I was typing that.
I was rehearsing. I was running really hard.
And then you're super stretchy, so...
I said, "You're so strong.
I mean, you're soaking wet.
But, she's saying that her stomach is split and she's sliding around.
What do you mean?What does that mean?
It says "sliding.
It's cool, though. It's a nice, clean swoosh.
You put roller shoes on?
Watch out.
I bought roller shoes recently.
I bought them, and when the guitar I wanted the most didn't arrive, I said, "Here, here, here," and it arrived.
Wow.
He was kind of skating around in the biggest mute.
Maybe I don't like it.
So, I'm just flying quietly, like, right here, right there.
Like, flying.
Hey. - Hey.
That's weird.
Can I help you?
Well, Guina's not here, so I was just saying...
Yes, ma'am.
Do you and Guina ever fight?
What?
But not like that.
Not at all.
I see.
Yes, I see.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
I've never hated you.
You can make a funny face if you don't like a word of it, can't you?
Ever.
You say it's because you're not here now.
I can't hear you.
I can't hear the gag.
You've got to be kidding me.
What was that?
Like, I'm sorry.
Yeah, I know.
It's not like we're fighting.
I don't know.
I don't know.I don't know.
Thank you for dinner.
What's the matter?
I'm just a little lost.
I don't want this to end.
Excuse me for a minute.
I always boo when I drink.
I forgot to leave the ocean where we're having dinner.
I told you to throw it in the ocean.
That's what I said.
And then...
When you look in the mirror.
There are times when you don't feel satisfied with yourself.
You look a little sleepy today.
Or your hair doesn't go all the way to the fringe.
If I tell you that your hair is a little messed up, you're going to get mad at me now.
Why?
Because you're cute.
Because of the way you look at yourself.
Is today a good day or is today a bad day?
I'm kind of having a bad day.
It's cute.
Next to that kind of thing
If you notice a little bit and you laugh
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm going to go over here more
Thank you very much.
You know what's been happening a lot lately?
When Emma's in rehearsal or at a gig or something.
"This song didn't go well.
She'd say, "You're singing it! She's like...
She's kind of complimentary.
It's kind of nice, isn't it?
It's zero-hard, right?
But it's cool. Zero spicy.
It's spicy, right?
I can't eat that, Japan.
Zero spice, right?
I can't eat it.
Have a potato and egg.
Here you go.Here you go.
One bottle for four.
I'm starving.
I was waiting for you to feed me.
And they keep coming.
Why is that?
It's hard.
They didn't smell the same.
Really?
They gave it to me by my hair.
I'm hungry.
I was waiting to feed you.
Oh!
Thanks for the food.
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
Today, it was the dessert of the meal,
It also means that I am a member of the Japan Gummy Association,
Let's eat gummy bears.
Wow.
Here you go.
Do you have any gummy bears that are hard or soft?
This one and this one.
Let's try both.
Yes, I'll try them both.
I don't think I've ever had these at home.
Yogurt flavor.
Open this one.
It's cute.
Thank you.
I think these would be good for Yuna.
Yuna-chan is going to have this.
What is it?
Afvangarg.
You're the youngest, right?
I see.
Yogurt flavor.
I'm supposed to click it with my teeth, but I don't have the strength.
I've tried to succeed once, so here.
I can't do this.I can't do this.
I can't do this.
Oh, I'm going to sleep.
Bon appétit.
Hey!
It's bursting.
Mmm.
Soda flavor?
No, I've got about five minutes left, in case you're wondering.
It's true.
Congratulations.
See you soon.
It's delicious. It's like this.
Yu had one the other morning.
Like in space.
It was like that for Yuna, but while she was doing various things,
Yuna and Yumindo and I are going together in the mountains.
That's right. The one in space.
That would be nice.
I'm sure they'll be eating kimchi at that time.
This is yogurt-flavored sushi.
Oh, man.
You call that amazing?
I mean small fish.
These are more like gummy bears,
They're gummy, but they're kind of like that.
Like jelly.
I've eaten them.
Which one of these do you like best that you've eaten?
Hmmm...
Fir.
Ah.
Hey, hey.
Jelly sushi is the best.
I like this.
Hey.
Curry is good, too.
Delicious.
Once the ice gummies started, I couldn't get any by hand.
So, I found these before, and I had them,And I found this one before, and I was holding it,
Yuno-chan was sleeping beside me.
But when I opened the ice gummy and started eating it, she got it without saying a word.
That's amazing.
Even when she was sleeping, she would do the same thing to the Gummi.
I wish you would tell me.
Yesterday, we were recording on the radio, and it just so happened,
Yuno was holding the gummy bear, and she left it there.
Then, naturally and spontaneously, she took the bag, opened it, and started eating it.
No? I said, "No, it's fine.
It's fine, it's totally fine.
Listen to me.
I always, absolutely, sometimes I'm allowed to get one.
That's right.
The first time, too, I tried to show it like this. I tried to show them like this.
But, as I thought, the staff members said, "What? How do you do this? I was asked, "How do you do this?
What? What do you mean? I thought.
So I just went out with this in my hand, just like normal, right?
But you opened it and started eating.
Well, it was interesting.
It was interesting.
It was long.
May I have this?
Sure.
Let's say this is a steering wheel.
I have a hard time using it.
I'm cherry-picking.
I'm making it into sugar.
I'm sugaring it.
Sweet.
Mmm.
Baby man.
I was watching.
Tendon man was my favorite.
That's a strange selection.
I liked Okin-chan.
We were together.
He's so cute.
Thank you for dinner.
How was it?
It was just a regular dinner party.It was just a regular dinner party.
I hope it's okay.
It was fun.
I got to eat a lot of gummy bears.
And I found some really good gummy bears.
How was it? Was it good?
I like the cherry blossoms.
I made a mistake.
Let's eat lots of gummi.
And do your best to get them from now on.
That's all I'm saying.
See you soon.
Subscribe to our channel and click the
Good Button
Please leave a comment.
Bye-bye!